- Previously on
"The Bachelorette"...
- I talked about the both
of you guys.
- What did you say, dude?
Just, what did you say?
- I didn't say
anything negative.
- Luke, no one believes you.
Nobody believes you!
- Really?
- I'm so frustrated.
- The person that's making her
feel bad is Luke.
- Luke, you need to stop
making excuses.
And we've talked about that.
But also,
stop the focus on him.
None of you know
anything about me
and why I'm here,
so I don't wanna do this.
- And tonight...
all: Hannah!
- I'm hopeful that I can get
everything turned back around
here in Latvia.
- You have no idea how much
I'm falling for you right now.
- Sometimes when you're
falling in love,
you just have
to take that leap.
[both screaming]
I'm going all in.
- Hannah went bungee jumping
naked with Garrett.
That was a slap in my face.
- You're not my husband.
You don't own my body.
You don't own me.
It's my body.
- You told her you were pissed
off at the way she acted.
- You gonna let me finish?
- No.
- Keep puffing your chest up,
bro.
- Keep your mouth shut and let
me get my point across.
- No, I'm--I'm not gonna keep
my mouth shut on this one.
- If you [bleep] up another
cocktail thing,
you're gonna have
me really pissed.
- Promise me that this
isn't gonna go into
tomorrow's Rose Ceremony.
- Why should I
promise you anything, man?
- Tell me that.
- Sweet dreams, Luke.
- It's all coming up tonight
on "The Bachelorette."
[folksy music]
♪ ♪
- We're in Riga, Latvia.
Riga is a beautiful city.
I feel like I'm in
a fairy tale movie that I used
to watch when I was
a little girl.
It looks like a set piece,
it's so beautiful.
♪ ♪
Last week in Scotland
was really hard
especially
at the Rose Ceremony.
I felt really defeated.
But I'm hopeful that I can get
everything turned back around
here in Latvia.
It seems like a great place
for a fresh start.
♪ ♪
I want this week to remind me
why I'm here,
and that is to find love and
to be romanced by these men.
I want a man
that fights for me,
goes on adventures with me,
and makes me feel loved.
I have a good feeling about
Riga and what it can bring.
♪ ♪
- Oh, my God.
[overlapping chatter]
Dude, this is sick.
[trolley bell ringing]
- Riga!
- Latvia!
- Wow, look at this building.
- Whoo!
- I am so excited to be here.
It's super romantic.
Definitely an easy spot
to fall in love.
I can't wait to see Hannah.
I want to see her right now.
- Dude, this is insane.
- Wow.
- We made it.
- There's only nine of us here
and I feel that Hannah
could see herself dating
every single one of us
outside of this setting.
- Oh, we're here.
- Yes, sir!
- Let's check it out.
What we got?
What're we working with?
- Ooh.
- Hey.
- We're getting down
to the nitty gritty.
- Look at that view.
- You might be leaving this
beautiful country in a few days
if you don't step up
to the plate.
all: Hannah!
- This week it's gonna be
important, you know,
how guys handle their
business in the house
and in front of her.
The guys gotta turn this
around
and get this thing right.
- I think all of us
need this week.
I mean, last Rose Ceremony
was really frustrating.
Bottom line is we don't want
anything to interrupt
our time with Hannah.
I know that was really
frustrating for me,
'cause I had to lie--I went
and laid it on the table.
- That frustration you felt is,
like, the frustration
a lot of us have had with you.
It's like a taste
of your own medicine.
- Yeah, but there's nothing
you can do if Hannah asks you
your opinion about somebody.
I mean--
- She said it best.
Just stay in your own lane.
Spend your time with her.
Make the most of it
and keep it moving.
[dramatic music]
[knocking]
- Ooh...
- I want my name to be
on the date card.
I mean, I'm hoping there's
another opportunity
for a one-on-one,
and if it's not,
it's a group date
and make the most of it.
- ♪ Duh duh duh duh ♪
guys: Ooh...
- Let's go.
♪ ♪
- "Garrett,
can I trust our love?
Love, Hannah."
- Yes, you can.
Man, I'm just so psyched.
- Seeing Garrett get
the one-on-one today,
it was like the first time
I was actually
legitimately jealous.
- Get out of here, man.
- Let's go, baby.
- Go get it.
- Get it, G.
- But I think there's
actually a good chance
that he goes home tonight
because she deserves guys
that genuinely
want to put their heart
on the table for her.
[dramatic music]
I know for a fact no guy here
feels about Hannah
the way I do.
I know that for a fact.
♪ ♪
- The fact that I got
a one-on-one,
God, it feels great.
It's something I've been
waiting on for a long time.
♪ ♪
I'm planning on just having
a great day with her
but at the same time the card
said, "Can I trust our love?"
And I wanna let her know that,
yeah, she can.
She shouldn't have
any doubts in it.
Got some very strong feelings
for the girl.
Look who it is.
- How are ya?
- I'm good.
How are you?
Good to see ya.
- I'm excited I get to spend
the whole day with Hannah
distraction-free, and it
doesn't matter what we do.
I'm just excited that Hannah's
along for the ride.
- Welcome to Latvia.
- This is incredible, huh?
- Yeah. I'm excited to explore
some of Latvia with you
and, you know, falling in love
is all about building trust,
so today I thought
we would work on that.
- Let's go.
So where are we going?
- Right now we're just walking
through the woods of Latvia.
I'm excited to hang out
with Garrett today.
He's definitely been a little
bit slower to open up.
I think today will help me see
what he can bring to the table
and if he can be a man that
I can trust him to go all in.
- I don't know
what we're doing.
I've been psyching myself up
this whole trip.
- Today Garrett and I are gonna
take a leap...for love.
- My mind's racing right now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
This is great.
- We're in Latvia.
Oh, look at that cable car.
- There's a cab--oh, shoot.
Oh, God! What?
[distant screaming]
[both screaming]
- Are they naked?
- They're naked?
- Wait, no, no, no, no, no.
- Yeah, they're naked.
What did you bring me to?
- They're butt-ass naked.
- Oh, my gosh.
[distant screams]
- Why are they naked?
- You tell me.
Why--
- [laughing]
- Does that help in some way?
You know, I thought I had
the upper hand on Garrett
because I knew that we were
bungee jumping and he didn't.
- Latvia's crazy, man.
- What I didn't know
is that Latvia people
bungee jump naked.
- Oh, this is--this is perfect.
- [laughs]
Perfect.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Welcome to Latvia.
- My name's Gunt.
- Hey, Garrett.
- Gunt.
- I'm Kristiana.
- Kristiana.
- Nice to meet you.
- A little, you see.
[all laughing]
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
- So?
- Everything will be fine.
You hear that?
All right.
- Have fun.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Good to meet y'all.
- Bye.
[quirky music]
- Oh, my God.
[laughing]
I did not know that
was gonna happen.
- You're not convincing me.
- No.
I swear on my life I did not
know that naked bodies
were about to fall
out of there.
- Holy crap.
A little speechless
at the moment.
Even in my worst-case scenario
of what the date could be today
I did not picture falling
naked out of a tram.
No.
[laughs]
I'm blushing.
Like...
[chuckles]
- My mom might kill me.
- There's nowhere to hide
right now.
Just gotta--just gotta
man up and do it.
We got this, I think.
I hope.
- [bleep] it.
When in Latvia,
you do it the Latvia way.
♪ ♪
- Here we go.
- Garrett and I get out
to the cable car
and I start freaking
the freak out.
Oh, my God!
I don't wanna do this.
- Hey, we've got this, okay?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Be strong, be courageous.
Be strong, be courageous.
Oh, my God.
Aah!
- I was like, "Holy crap."
But this is an opportunity
to show her
that I'm here for her.
We'll be okay.
That doesn't mean I'm any less
scared right now.
- Oh--oh, my God.
I don't know how high
up we are.
Ohh!
[murmuring]
- All right, we've got this.
- Okay, copy that.
- Okay.
It's gonna be fine.
- We'll be fine.
- Aah!
It's freezing.
- Hang on.
We'll be laughing
about it soon.
- Okay.
- All right?
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Here we go!
- Oh, my God, no!
Here we go!
We got this, all right?
- Okay, got it.
- I'll be right there with you.
- I'm scared.
- Ooh!
- In the past I have let
my fear of what people
think of me control
my actions.
Oh, what are we doing?
But that's the old Hannah.
I will not allow fear
to control me.
[laughs]
Oh, my freak!
I just want to live
in the moment
and do what feels right.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
No fear.
- No fear.
♪ ♪
- Are you ready?
- [exhales]
- Okay, tell me
when you're ready.
I don't know.
Okay.
Oh, my--oh, [bleep],
I'm not--okay.
Tell me when you're ready.
- All right.
We can be strong.
On three, okay?
- Okay.
- All right.
We've got this, all right?
I'm right here with you.
- Are you ready?
- I'm ready when you're ready.
- Okay.
- You trust me?
- I trust you.
- All right.
- One, two, three, go.
[both screaming]
[continue screaming]
- Oh, my God!
[upbeat music playing]
- [laughing, screaming]
We did it!
- Come here,
you beautiful woman.
♪ ♪
- [laughing]
Oh, my gosh.
Today was freaking badass.
I think that deserves
one of these.
- [chuckling]
Whoo!
- Whoo!
We freaking did it.
- It felt nice to be free
from the restriction
of clothing.
It felt like freedom.
both: Whoo!
We were both terrified.
But Garrett the whole time
was like, "Oh, we got this.
We got this."
He was like, "Trust me."
And in the end it was fun.
[mellow music]
- How great was that?
- You didn't even flinch when I
pulled a surprise at the end.
- You're right.
- Why?
[laughs]
My mind was, uh, on...
- Other things.
- The 100 yards of drop
that we had.
- I mean,
I do have a nice booty.
- [laughs] I'm so happy
we did that, though.
I feel closer.
- I definitely feel closer
after that.
- I feel closer.
Yeah.
- Yeah, you were very strong.
And that's what I want
in a man,
and you definitely
showed that today.
- Well--
- And I appreciate that.
- It's really good
to see you smiling again.
It, uh, honestly it really,
like, tugged at my heart
to see you cry the other day.
- Well, I appreciate
you saying that.
I hated that...
♪ ♪
That Rose Ceremony--or cocktail
party--went the way it did.
- With the arguments happening,
the attention was off
what was important...
- Mm-hmm.
- Was the fact of it is--and
I know it taught me a lesson.
I agree to leave
everything behind.
I'm only focusing on you
right now.
All right?
- Okay.
I appreciate that.
- You're welcome.
♪ ♪
- Today's date with Garrett
was the fresh start
that I hoped for.
Garrett was exactly
what I needed today
and what I asked for today.
He was like,
"We're doing this.
"We've got this.
But I'm also terrified
just like you are."
♪ ♪
I think that's a lot
like falling in love.
You're terrified
but you're also excited
and happy that you
took the risk.
[church bell ringing]
[soft music]
- How are you feeling?
- I'm feeling a little
warmer right now.
- [laughs]
Today with Garrett was
really a great start
to this week in Riga.
- After you.
- Bungee jumping was really
fun and it was so freeing.
And we conquered
a fear together.
- Ooh.
- Isn't it beautiful?
I feel like my relationship
with Garrett
is definitely growing.
But, you know, I hope that
Garrett and I can get past
all the adrenaline and have
a more serious conversation
to continue on a beautiful day.
- You look great.
You look fantastic.
- Oh, thank you.
- I wanna give a quick cheers
to all of the sights
that Latvia had to offer today.
- They were great sights.
[laughs]
- Cheers.
- Today was so fun.
When that couple came out,
I kind of looked down
and I saw all his goods
and I'm like, "Oh, crap.
"Yep, that is a real ding dong
in front of me.
Okeydokey."
- [laughs]
Just send it.
Let it all hang loose.
- Hey.
- You know?
- Hang loose.
- But it meant a lot that you
were so vulnerable today.
- [laughs]
- Both emotionally
and physically.
It made me feel
very comfortable.
It made me feel very confident
where we're at right now.
I mean, I feel like when
you're pressed against a wall
like what we were,
you just really find out
a lot about the other person
who's right there next to ya.
- Mm-hmm.
And even though, like,
you were out of your element,
you still showed up.
And I think that's been your
journey here with me.
You know, a little hesitant
at first,
but as soon as you realized
that were doing this thing,
you--
- We're doing it.
- You were doing it.
- So heights were, like,
a really, really, really
big hurdle for me.
- Mm-hmm.
- Big time.
So what's, like, a big hurdle
in your life that you've had
that's helped mold you?
- Um, I think for me
there's been a lot.
But I think really just
living my life
for myself and not, like,
letting others control
what I do.
And so, like,
I would do everything
everybody wanted me to
or be the person
everybody wanted me to be
because I didn't want
to be rejected.
Rejection is, like, all fear.
- Yeah.
- And I've, like, allowed
that fear to control me.
And it's hard and it's
a battle every single day
but it's gotten
a lot easier to fight.
And I have the right weapons
to bring to the battle now.
But that was something today
that I kept thinking is, like,
"I don't want this fear
to control me."
- And that's why there was no
way I was backing down today.
Even though every ounce of me
wanted to back down big time.
But I'm not gonna back down
any time soon.
I hope I proved that
to you today,
and I hope I keep proving it
to you from here on out.
- You definitely did
prove that today.
That was really attractive.
[laughs]
[train bells dinging]
[knocking]
- Uh-oh.
- I hope I get a one-on-one
date card.
I think it means a lot.
Some of you guys have already
had a one-on-one.
You've had that
boyfriend-girlfriend feeling.
The rest of us need more time.
- I'm in the same boat as you.
You haven't had one-on-one.
I haven't had a one-on-one.
Peter, you haven't had
a one-on-one.
So if it's a group date,
you don't want to hear
your name called at this point,
right?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- All right, it's a group date.
Mike,
Jed,
Tyler,
Dustin,
Luke,
Connor,
Dylan.
"Let's discover Riga!
Love, Hannah."
- You're a good dude, Peter.
You deserve this.
- Have fun.
- You guys,
you gotta remember,
if there's two one-on-ones
next week,
it may be the two of you,
so...
- Gotta get to next week.
♪ ♪
- Uh, I grew up, actually--
I don't know if you know this,
but in a big time
football family.
My dad played football
in college.
My brother and I both
played football.
And so that was, like,
my whole life thinking
I was born and bred
for one thing.
And looking back on it,
it's because not only
I thought it was something
I should do
but something that felt like
others wanted me to do,
so I did it.
And, uh, I realized that,
you know,
I actually hated football.
And it led me into golf.
And that's just one of those
things where, like,
I'm just a firm believer,
if you do what you want to do
and not what other people
want you to do
and you just trust it,
it's gonna work out.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's funny the way it is when
you think about it, you know?
It's just--it's kinda like
what we did today, you know?
- Mm-hmm.
- Just dive in if
you're gonna dive in.
No point in holding back,
and here we are.
- I think you just have
to trust through all that
and know that, like,
there's always gonna be
a greater good that, like, all
things work together for good.
- It's almost like I keep
relating back to today,
but today just reminded me
of a lot of things, too.
It was--
- Mm-hmm.
- It--it--it's very symbolic
in a way, I should say.
'Cause we were on the platform
and then we held each other
and we trusted each other
and we took a leap of faith
and trusted that
the dang thing would hold,
and what do you know?
Good things happened
in the end, right?
- Yeah.
[laughs]
- But honestly, it's--it
is a lot like falling in love.
Right?
- Mm-hmm.
- You hold on for dear life
and trust each other,
take a leap of faith,
and hope something good
happens in the end, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- And I had the same feeling
right now right before
that--I jumped off that tram
with you today.
Heart's racing a good bit.
- [laughs]
- I'm laying the cards
on the table.
I'm falling in love for you.
Big time.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I'm smiling so big.
[laughs]
Today, I did not want to jump.
But you allowed me
to feel so free
in a moment that I thought
I would never do.
Sometimes when you're
falling in love,
you just have to trust
and take that leap.
So with that, Garrett,
will you accept this rose?
- Yes, ma'am.
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
Today with Garrett
was so special.
Garrett is strong,
he's fun,
and funny,
and Garrett feels like home.
Thank you.
It already feels so much more
romantic than where we were
a few days ago.
[cello playing]
♪ ♪
You want to dance?
- Dance?
- [laughs]
The first day I got here
in Latvia, I mean,
I did not feel very good about
this whole experience.
But after tonight,
I feel a lot better
and a lot more hopeful.
I feel back on track
to find love.
Tonight was so magical.
I mean, what a way
to open up your heart.
[soft classical music]
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
- We decided
to bungee jump naked.
- Naked?
- Naked.
- This is a woman that I want
to spend the rest
of my life with, and that was
a slap in my face.
There's definitely a big thing
I want to share with you.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna be honest.
You're not gonna like this.
[tense chords]
- You told her you were pissed
off at the way she acted.
- Are you gonna let me finish?
- No.
- Keep puffing your chest up,
bro.
- Keep your mouth shut and let
me get my point across.
- No, I'm not gonna keep
my mouth shut on this one.
- If you [bleep] up another
cocktail thing,
you're gonna have me
really pissed.
- What's up, big dog?
- What's up, guys?
- Tell us about last night,
bro.
- Did you face any fears?
- My gut feeling was correct.
It had something
to do with heights.
Dude, I don't think
y'all realize,
I've never been on
a roller coaster before
'cause I'm that afraid
of heights.
- Dude, that's insane.
- Yeah, and, um, I meet her
kinda by this bridge
and, yeah, a naked Latvian
couple bungee jumped out.
[overlapping murmuring,
chuckles]
And so we decided
to bungee jump naked.
- Naked?
- Naked.
- How was bungee jumping?
I mean, like--
- I essentially
was hugging her
and she was hugging me,
and she put her shoulder
and her head right here.
Dude, it was--it was cool,
man, 'cause she--
I mean, you find out what
a person's made of
under pressure like that.
When it was game time,
switch just flicked on
and she was all game for it,
man.
- I'm hearing Garrett's story
and I don't--
I don't know
if that's how it went down.
- Oh, wow.
- That's wild.
- It was awesome, yeah.
- Who would want to be naked
with that guy?
There's no way Hannah
went bungee jumping naked
with Garrett.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
[dog barks]
- Today I'm excited to roam
the streets of Riga.
I can't wait to have
a normal date...
with seven men,
which is not normal,
but I just want it to be fun.
Yesterday's one-on-one with
Garrett went really well.
It felt like a reset
from the Rose Ceremony
fiasco in Scotland.
Hey!
[both laughing]
I am cautiously optimistic
about how today will go.
Welcome to the Riga
marketplace.
So I thought today would just
be fun to just explore
this amazing city.
- Let's do it.
- Okay, let's go.
We're doing all the things.
- All right.
- Whoo!
- Oh, my God.
- Fishy, fishy.
- Smells like our breakfast,
though.
- Dude, some of these
look terrifying.
- Come on, Dylan.
- I mean, I'm gonna eat them
if we have to.
- You gonna eat them?
Okay.
- Uh-oh.
- Is that tequila?
- Ooh.
Vodka?
- Moonshine.
all: Moonshine!
- There we go!
- Whoo!
This is awesome.
- Let's just toast to a great
day and moonshine.
all: Prieka!
- Whoo!
I mean, that feels good, y'all.
Don't y'all feel good?
That felt good.
- Today's going great.
- Pickles!
- You know, there was
a lot of B.S.
that went down in Scotland
and it's great to see her
kind of refresh and recharge
here in Riga.
- Somebody's eating
one of these.
[all shouting]
Oh, shoot!
- Everyone's kind of getting
along and, you know,
I think everyone really
listened to Hannah's message.
And I wanted to get her
something, you know,
to make her feel special.
Excuse me, fellas.
I got something for you.
- Oh, my gosh!
- For you, Hannah B.
You like them?
- Today's been an amazing day.
We've had a lot of fun.
- Cheese!
I love a good cheese.
- I just want Hannah
to have a good time.
- String cheese!
- It's good to see her happy.
That's all I want.
She's an amazing woman.
You look so beautiful.
I'm glad to be here.
I need you to give me a chance
to be there for you.
I wanna be your all,
you know what I mean?
- Can we, uh, can we get back
to our group date, please?
- [laughing] Oh, yes.
Let's do it.
- Riga!
[upbeat music playing]
♪ ♪
- Everything seems really good
with Hannah.
I can tell that she's happy
and having a good time
and it's good to see her let
loose and just be herself.
[singing in foreign language]
But this isn't easy for me.
This is not the ideal
scenario whatsoever,
but, I mean, that's the dynamic
of a group date is, you know,
I'm sharing her.
♪ ♪
- Today is so fun.
Three, two, one, go!
[all shouting]
And today is exactly what
I needed today to be.
Everybody's getting along.
[screams]
All the men, they all did
exactly what I asked,
and it made me feel so good.
- The train's coming.
Let's go.
- And I haven't felt that
in a while.
And so it's exactly
what I needed,
more than I even could
hope for, honestly.
Y'all, let me tell you
this story
that is part of, like,
the Latvian tradition,
nude bungee jumping.
So, anyways, these people come
out and I'm like,
"Look at them.
They're butt naked."
So I--I can't even, like, talk.
I'm, like,
"Um, yeah, hey, what's up?
Mmm."
And they're like,
"It's tradition
to do bungee jumping
naked as couples."
And I was like--
- Is this, like, when you're
an official couple
kind of tradition or--
- Huh?
No, just like a thing.
And so I was like,
if I went to a nude beach,
I would go nude.
Like, you just gotta--you gotta
do what--what you do there.
So I was like,
"I'm gonna do it."
- Jeez.
It's true.
Naked.
- It was awesome.
It was like the best
experience ever.
- I'm shocked.
Just the sheer fact, I mean...
[tense music]
- Oh, this is our stop, guys.
- This is a woman
that I want to
spend the rest
of my life with, and...
totally thought that was...
crossing the line.
[bell tolling]
- This is St. Peter's Church.
It's over 800 years old.
- Like, her body
is her temple.
And to expose it to anyone
who isn't her husband--
that was--that was a slap
in my face.
- Can we just, like,
hold hands?
In this whole journey, like,
I've definitely struggled.
I'm not perfect and I don't
ever plan to act like I am.
- If she really is the one for
me--which I believe she is--
there's a lot of answers
that I need.
I have to say something.
[dramatic chords]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[train bell ringing]
- Hannah, you look lovely.
- Aww, thanks, Jed.
- I was gonna say I can
smell you from here.
You smell great.
- Aww, thank you.
Take a leftie.
Today was so fun.
We had the best time
just laughing
and taking in the culture
together.
Welcome to my palace.
- Oh-ho!
- It's such a breath of fresh
air to just have a good day
and a good night.
What?
Is that a real thing?
Thank y'all so much for today.
I feel like today has
just been a reset.
I'm just so proud of you guys.
Like, you set differences aside
and it felt really, really fun
just being with you all.
And so I just want to make
a toast to, um,
you all just stepping up today.
- Yeah.
- Thank you for making me
so hopeful for tonight
and for the rest
of the journey we have ahead.
So, cheers to romance in Riga.
I love that.
- To romance in Riga.
- Cheers!
- Riga.
- Riga!
- [clears throat]
On that note,
can I grab you, Hannah?
- Yeah.
- All right.
♪ ♪
- Let's go.
- Yes.
- I had to kidnap you first.
Sorry.
- No, I know.
I like it.
- All right.
Oh, man.
♪ ♪
Last two weeks have been tough
for you, you know?
- Mm-hmm.
- But, no, today was amazing.
- It was so fun.
And I want to say that you took
so many moments with me
to make me feel so special.
It just means a lot to me.
- Mm-hmm.
And I thought today was a great
day 'cause it wasn't like
a crazy group date.
I had this moment
that hit me so hard,
it kind of shook me,
freaked me out.
- Mm-hmm.
- But it was when you
came waking in
on the Rose Ceremony night
and you were wearing all white.
I mean, you looked Heaven-sent.
You were like an angel.
And I--I pray to God
that you're my angel, you know?
Then later on, like,
you held it down, like,
between all of us.
Stood there
and--and--and fought.
- What did you think
when I walked in?
- You had this look where you
were just all business.
And I was like,
"That's what I want."
You know what I mean?
At the house.
Like, I want that, you know?
'Cause you're gonna have kids
and you're gonna have things
that you gotta stand up for
and fight for,
and where did this fighter
come from?
'Cause I adore it.
♪ ♪
I really do feel like
I am falling in love
with this girl.
She's a strong woman and,
I mean,
she's--she's got the ability
to move mountains.
♪ ♪
Like, I've seen so many
aspects of Hannah
and all of them have been
something I've adored
and wanted and--just, like,
long for in my future.
I really believe
I'm the guy for her
at the end of all this.
I just wanna keep making you
feel special.
When I'm with her,
I really just don't think
about anything else.
It's just me and her.
- All right.
- [laughs]
- So this is your song, "Home."
♪ ♪
- This is so hot.
It's so hot.
[soft piano notes]
♪ ♪
[moving melody]
- I'm just happy
today went well.
Hopefully tonight
goes even better.
- I don't know about you guys,
but I was just not comfortable
with how that whole
one-on-one went down
with the whole bungee
jumping thing.
I was took back.
You know what I mean?
Like, bare skin, like,
being topless.
I'm like, "Hold up, hold up.
What?"
- Here's where I differ,
though is I actually, like,
respect and love that
she went for it.
She's making her own decisions.
She's not making any decisions
for anyone else but herself.
Let her go have
those experiences,
live them to the max.
She's living Riga
to the fullest.
- I definitely wanna make sure
that Hannah and I
are on the same page.
There's a lot I wanna get
off my chest.
But at the same time
if all goes through as planned,
I'm definitely getting
the Group Date Rose.
Did you have a good time today?
- I did.
- Yeah?
- Did you?
- I had a great time.
- Good.
- Um--
- How are you doing?
- I'm doing really well.
I wanna hear a lot honestly
just from you,
but there's definitely a big
thing I wanna share with you.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna be honest.
You're not gonna like this.
- Okay.
- Like, have you ever been...
cheated on
in your relationship?
- Mm-hmm.
- You know that feeling?
- Yeah.
- Like, your stomach, like,
it's like it turns inside out,
it's just twisted.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm not gonna lie.
I had that feeling
this morning.
You know, we were about to get
sent off for the group date
and Garrett started blurting
out a whole bunch of stuff
about what happened with you
guys on the one-on-one.
And honestly, like, it's hard
for me to receive,
and it's just because I know
that your body is a temple
and honestly, like,
I'm just thinking of you
holding him bare-skinned
and I'm just thinking
in my mind, like...
[huffs]
It really pissed me off.
I mean, it really
frustrated me.
- I had a choice,
what I wanted to do.
And, like, I know where my
heart was in it,
and it wasn't in a sexual way.
It was in an experience that,
like, I wanted to have
for myself.
- Right.
But still at the same time,
like, I mean,
I'm looking for you
to meet my family soon,
and I felt like it was
a slap in the face.
But no matter what you do,
like, I'm going to support you.
Even if you make
a boneheaded mistake
and you just do something
completely
out of your character
and something that's wrong,
I'm gonna do whatever it is
to make things right.
I'm--I'm in this,
and we're gonna work
through this together
and I'm not worried about it.
I just want you to know that
at the end of the day,
no matter what, like,
we're gonna get
through anything.
And I feel that way.
I had to address
the Garrett thing.
I'd been thinking about it
and sour about it all day.
Just the thought of it crossing
my mind pissed me off.
You asked me to be real and I
wanted you to know, like,
what was on my--weighing on my
mind and my heart.
It feels really good
to get it off my chest
and just completely be myself
and be real.
This conversation I think
will definitely help her
understand me better.
I mean, I know that we can
work through anything.
♪ ♪
- Tonight was so great.
And it was a great continuation
of a wonderful day.
And that was
because of all you guys.
But...
I want to give this rose
to Tyler.
You were just awesome today.
So, Tyler, will you
accept this rose?
- Always.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Oh, man.
- That sucks.
I was completely real, open,
and honest with Hannah,
but I didn't get the rose.
- And I think, uh, Riga has
a special place for all of us.
And it was, uh, an amazing day.
- I think so, too.
- You know, it sucks but
at the end of the day,
I'm confident that I'm gonna
get that final rose.
And that's the only thing
that matters to me.
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
- Oh, my God!
- I literally have no idea
where I'm at right now.
But, hey, I'm game
for whatever it is.
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
- We burnt it down
with our fire.
- And then...
- Luke, can I talk to you
for a second?
- Yes.
- She didn't look too happy.
- Hannah is putting one and two
and three together.
- The train is finally
on the track.
- I don't know!
You don't own my body.
You don't own me.
You're not my husband.
[dramatic musical sting]
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
- Today I'm in
the Latvian countryside.
I have been trying really hard
this week to really
open my heart up.
I really am.
I don't wanna go through this
and know that I didn't
give it my all.
I'm embracing what this is,
going all in.
And, like, I'm so excited
about Peter.
- I think I see someone.
- [laughs]
There is a lot about Peter
that would be amazing
for the rest of my life.
He's the guy you wanna see
pushing a stroller in a park.
I have a fun date
in store for us.
- I like it.
- Yeah?
- Let's do it.
- Today we are going to have
a Latvian-style spa day.
[both laughing]
I think it's perfect timing
for Peter
to have all of me today
like he deserves.
- Hello!
- Hello.
- Hello, welcome to Latvia.
- Thank you.
- All right.
- Oh, my God.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- I like it.
- Oh!
- I like the Latvian look.
I literally have no idea
where I'm at right now.
But, hey, I'm all for it.
It's adventure.
I know Hannah brings
the adventure,
so I'm game for whatever it is.
- Hi.
- Wait, you call it what?
- Pirts.
- Peer--pits?
- It's intimate place where
you can open your heart
and be the real person
which you are.
- I like that.
- Pirts for couples
could be the place
where they could
get closer to each other.
You never will be the same
like you was before.
- Ooh.
- [laughs]
- I like that.
Okay.
- So then before we start,
we want you to go
to change clothes.
- Okay.
- Pirts, it's like
a cleansing ritual.
It's a tradition that,
you know, the Latvian people,
they use frequently.
It's just two souls in sync
with each other
and keeping that good energy.
I'm just excited to experience
new cultures with Hannah.
- [singing in native language]
♪ ♪
- That was beautiful.
- Thank you.
- [singing in native language]
♪ ♪
And slowly we can move
closer to the plants.
- Ooh, I like this tea.
- So what do we have here?
- Pick which you want.
- We're making
some honey sauce
to put on our bodies.
- It gives you feeling,
"Oh, I am wonderful woman."
- That was my favorite one.
- This calms down
overheated mind.
- Peter must put this.
- Must put this one in?
- Put more.
- A little bit more?
- Yeah.
- It's like spices, some
concoction that you can make.
They have literally a spice
for everything it seems like.
- It helps you to recognize
true love.
- Let me do an extra old dose
of that one.
- There we go!
I've never done anything
like this in my entire life,
but, hey, I'm with Hannah
so I'm ready to do it.
[upbeat music]
- Beautiful.
You did it before, I think.
[whack]
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- You kinda like just wash
away any negative energy
and just like cleanse
the person of that.
How you feeling?
- I just got caught
in a tornado in Alabama.
- Now it's time that
we go to Pirts
to try yourself.
- All right, let's do it.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
[soft music]
- Ooh!
- Okay.
- So take the robes...
- Take your robes off.
- The chemistry's there
with Peter.
Like,
there's no denying that.
I like that Peter always
makes me feel special,
that he's into me,
and that he's here for me.
♪ ♪
- So the first thing
we always do,
we put three fingers inside
the water and we make a wish
for today.
- I wish to have
an amazing experience,
um, that allows me
to open my heart
for receiving love that
is uncondit--unconditional.
♪ ♪
- I just ask that you allow
Hannah and I
to, uh, truly embrace this
and use this as a way
to come together and always
just being our truest self
with each other.
I never in my wildest dreams
would have thought
I'd ever be in Latvia doing
a bonding spiritual experience
with such an amazing girl.
This is such an amazing
opportunity
to come together as a couple
and leave even more attached
than we were before.
Like, this is so much adventure
and like this is what I crave.
I want a lifetime of this.
I like this sweaty look.
- I like the sweaty look.
- I'm feeling it.
- I like a man dirty
and sweaty and I mean,
you were just beat
with some leaves.
- I like that.
♪ ♪
- With Peter and I, I mean,
it's just like
so sexually driven.
Like, so hot.
Our physical connection
is a ten out of ten.
♪ ♪
- If this works out
with her and I,
we are 100% getting a sauna
at her place.
I know, like, we have
something very strong here.
And, like, I'm ready to show
her that fire and fight
till the end and make sure
she knows that, like,
I'm not one of those guys
that's been involved
with all this drama.
Definitely wanna just like
talk to you about, like,
from the Scotland night.
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, just being
completely honest,
um, like, it really--that hurt
me a lot, like,
seeing you in that state.
- Mm-hmm.
- It sucked, I guess,
when you kinda, like,
grouped me in with, like,
everyone else.
You know, like,
the whole group,
not knowing, like, if you could
see yourself getting there
with any of us.
Like, I just want you
to know that I am...
So all about this.
I have literally had one focus,
and I just want you to know,
like, what you have with me,
you know?
I promise to give you, like,
that fire and be that rock
for you to, like,
lean on at all times,
'cause when I commit, like,
I'm there.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know?
I am all in.
I'm loving where it's going,
and I really like you.
- I have no doubts...
- Good.
- That you're all in for me.
But because I am so
comfortable with you,
I wanna know more about you,
and I'm excited for time
to get to do that.
- No, I can tell you--
- Moving forward, you know?
- I love this.
You know, this--I've been
wanting this for a while,
this one-on-one with you,
'cause I've seen
so much potential with this,
and I wanna--
I wanna learn everything
about you, you know?
All those secrets and the
good things and bad things.
I can tell, like,
you're a very special girl
and there's a lot to you.
- And you have to know
that I'm actually crazy.
- You might be a little crazy.
- If you can handle it.
- But I'm okay with crazy.
I like crazy.
You know?
Crazy keeps it fun.
♪ ♪
- I like that Peter
makes me feel like a woman.
Yet again, we burnt it down
with our fire.
♪ ♪
But tonight I really need
to dive a little bit deeper
into our relationship.
[gentle piano music]
♪ ♪
- You look handsome.
- Well, you look beautiful,
as always.
- Thank you.
- Well, this is beautiful
over here.
- I know, yeah.
- All right.
- During the day with Peter,
I mean,
it was hot in every sense.
- Wow, this--this is perfect.
- [laughs]
- I love this.
- And it's so funny, 'cause
Peter is so sweet and gentle,
but when it's go time
with Peter, it's go time.
To the best and hottest...
- Yes, for sure.
- Experience.
- I'm getting hot just thinking
about it right now.
- [laughs]
- That was so hot.
- It was so hot.
We obviously have chemistry,
but I want to know
if there is substance
behind that chemistry.
- So, Hannah Brown,
since, like, day one,
I've, like, seen this,
like, strength and confidence.
Like, where does
that come from?
- It's all--that's how I've
always been as a little girl.
Like, I mean, like,
I'm the most introverted person
in my family.
- You are not.
- Yes, I am.
- There's no way.
- I think I've always had
like a spitfire-type
personality.
It was always--it's who I am.
I think a lot of times,
the perfect woman
is supposed to be
quiet and gentle,
and that is the perfect woman
for someone,
but that's not me.
- That's not you at all.
I love that firecracker,
though, you know?
I love that strength
that I see in you.
Seriously, I do.
You know,
I kind of draw my strength
a lot from, honestly,
what I do for work.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know, just--
you can't fail
'cause, you know,
you have lives in your hands
every single flight.
- Well, I'm really fascinated
by your job.
Seriously,
I think it's super hot.
[both laugh]
But your career
is get up and go,
and you're going
place to place.
How has that affected
your dating life?
- For me, as great as,
you know,
my job is,
and I love what I do,
it can get lonely if I don't
have someone to share it with.
- Yeah, have you shared it
with someone in the past?
- Um...
yeah, so, it was very serious,
and, you know, we felt
very deeply for each other.
Um, but...
it just, uh--it
just wasn't meant to be.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know, and...
I mean, I guess, you know,
bringing that up,
it has been...
being very truthful with you.
Like, it has been
kind of difficult for me
to, you know, truly,
like, open up 100%
and...take, like, those guards
down around the heart 'cause,
like, I truly have not allowed
myself to open up my heart
for someone since that last
relationship just because
it was--it was--it was like
my biggest form of heartbreak
that I've ever felt, and I was
like devastated from it.
And I'm not gonna lie:
it's scary with you
because, like, honest to God,
from my heart, like,
I've never felt so strongly
for someone so quickly.
And, like...like, I really
am falling for you.
And it's a scary feeling but
it's such a beautiful feeling
because I've not let
that happen for so long.
My grandmother,
who I was super close to,
she always would tell my mom
this saying,
and then my mom would always
tell me this saying.
It goes, like...
[speaking Spanish]
And essentially that means,
"Son, don't worry, don't fret.
"Let the waters run.
"Let the river, you know,
flow as it may
"because what's for you
and what's meant for you
will never be tarnished
and will always be yours."
And in my mind, it's just,
like, all coming together
and it's, like,
this could be the reason
why all that other stuff
didn't work out.
You know,
this could be something
super special
between the two of us.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- Thank you so much for, um...
being vulnerable with me.
That's, like, exactly...
[sighs]
What I not only wanted
but needed from you tonight.
And I can relate
to closing my heart up
after, like, a huge heartbreak,
and, like, I have talked
about being engaged twice.
Like, I've been in love,
truly, twice.
Ultimately, neither
one of them were my person,
and I can see I know that,
but that's why I know I'm here.
Like, I had to go
through all that.
- Sure, yeah.
- It's so crazy.
- Let the waters run.
- Yeah.
- I wanna know every bit
of your heart, seriously.
- Same.
- At the end of this,
like, I want...
I wanna know it all.
- If you keep giving it to me,
I'll give it back.
- All right, deal.
[tender music]
- Um, I know you had
to wait a little while...
- It was all worth the wait.
- [laughs]
- Trust me.
- But even from
our first conversation,
there was no denying
that we have chemistry.
But tonight really solidified
that we have connections
far beyond physical,
and that's all
that I can ask for,
and today makes me really
excited for what's to come.
So I have this.
- What's that?
Look at that.
Where'd that come from?
- Peter, will you
accept this rose?
- 100% over and over and over.
- Thank you.
- I'm falling
for Hannah, like,
faster that I've ever
fallen for someone.
I love the strength
that she has
and the confidence and
the sexiness and the goofiness
and the cuteness and
the craziness and just, like,
the humor and just--I just--
yeah, everything about her.
It's great.
All right.
How lucky are we?
Like, I am so high right now
on cloud nine,
Like, I'm loving this.
This is absolutely stunning.
[tender music]
[fireworks whistle]
Oh, my God!
- [gasps]
[laughs]
- Shut up!
[fireworks popping]
- I like that Peter's a man
and that he makes me
feel like a woman.
Tonight's conversation
really proved to me
that my feelings for him
have validity.
And now I'm looking at him
as a life partner.
I want us to keep growing,
and I want him to continue
to open up to me because
I wanna open my heart to him.
- You have no idea how much
I'm falling for you right now.
Like, I am in.
I am so in right now.
[dramatic romantic music]
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
- I've been so excited
because our relationship
has finally been on track,
but, like, it's closer--
- It's not on track.
No, I don't--no!
- She didn't look too happy.
- You gonna let me finish?
- No.
- That's your [bleep] fault,
homie.
- He's a joke, man.
- What was that?
- Oh, you're trying to be
a big dog again.
- Let's just
keep it down here--
- Would you do me a favor
and keep your mouth shut?
[dramatic music]
Promise me that this
isn't gonna go
into tomorrow's Rose Ceremony.
- Why should I promise you?
- Tell me that.
- Sweet dreams, Luke.
[train clanking]
[tense music]
- I'm expecting Peter to come
home from his one-on-one.
I think we all know
Peter's a good dude,
but it was tough for me today,
guys.
I mean,
it was tough last night
reading the one-on-one
date card,
especially when it said,
"Let's heat things up."
- You've just gotta trust
that she's making
the right decisions and she's
doing what's best for her
when she does these
one-on-ones, you know?
- Yeah.
- You gotta just focus
on your moments with her
and, you know, do your best to
kind of like block out the--
what you don't want
to think about
and don't want to see.
[door clicks]
- What's up, guys?
- Hey!
- What's going on?
- What's up?
- There he is!
- Whoo! That was--
It was fireworks, for sure.
- What'd y'all do?
- Had a blast.
So we went to kind of
like the middle of the woods
and had no idea
what was going on.
We went to, like--
like, a sauna,
and, uh, it was like a really
just good, like...
- I miss Hannah,
and it's really hard
to see her
go on dates with other people.
[dramatic music]
- It was a very good time
in the sauna, so...
- I know I just saw her
yesterday, but, like,
you know,
I'm falling for this girl,
and I'm just, like,
trying to figure it all out,
and it's hard
to put into words,
but I just know that
I want to do whatever I can
to get to spend time
with Hannah.
[dramatic music]
[gentle guitar music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ I'll be
your Mr. Right, girl ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'll be
your Mr. Right, girl ♪
- Oh!
♪ ♪
- ♪ And, Hannah, Hannah ♪
- Oh, me?
[giggles]
- ♪ I'll never tell a lie ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I wanna come inside ♪
- [laughs]
Well, hey, come on in.
- All right, all right.
- [laughs]
[gentle guitar music]
Cute Mr. Jed
calling out to me,
strumming on his guitar
singing a song.
Oh!
If that's not
out of a romance novel...
How cool is this?
I don't know what is.
[plucky guitar music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Wanna pull you close ♪
♪ Whisper in your ear ♪
♪ Tell you I want you ♪
♪ Right here ♪
♪ Wanna let these hands ♪
♪ Glide down your sides ♪
♪ Tell a story with my lips ♪
♪ Slide that dress
up your thigh ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You never know
when it might be over ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You never know
when our time may end ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Is it really a sin ♪
♪ To be skin to skin? ♪
♪ To look into your soul
and tell you how I feel? ♪
♪ No, it can't be so bad ♪
♪ To wanna love you this way ♪
♪ Every time I have to leave ♪
♪ You make me wanna stay ♪
- Mmm.
That was very nice.
[laughs]
[giggles]
And you are very fine.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
- Mind if you come out here,
have a little bit of a talk?
- Yeah, man.
- I was told by multiple
members of the group
that you brought up our
one-on-one date with Hannah,
and you expressed to her
that you didn't appreciate
what she did...
- Right.
- During the one-on-one date.
- Now, me bringing it up again
was something
I didn't even wanna do.
I wanted to tuck it
under the rug,
but something that I've been
struggling with
with Hannah, and Hannah's told
me specifically, "Luke,
when you feel a certain way,
like, I want you to show me."
I did express to her
that it pissed me off
because the way
you explained it to us,
I thought it was a lack
of respect for Hannah.
- I agree to disagree,
man, but I just think that
asking Hannah about details
on a date that you weren't on,
that was coming out
of your lane.
- I'm not getting in your lane,
but when I'm driving in my lane
and I look over and I see
Hannah with you,
metaphorically speaking,
when you explain
your one-on-one date,
and I see
something that concerns me,
I just want clarity.
I never went in your lane.
I wasn't ever telling her
how and what
she can or can't do
with her body.
- I don't care.
- I just wanted more details.
I feel like I needed it.
Now, for you to look at me and
say, "You shouldn't need that,"
now, that's you
coming into my lane.
Listen, she's your girlfriend,
but she's also mine,
so it's my business,
and I just wanna make sure
this right now
is not brought up
at the Rose Ceremony.
- Why is it your business
what Hannah and I talk about
at tomorrow's Rose Ceremony?
- Can you just promise me
that this isn't
gonna go into tomorrow's
Rose Ceremony?
[tense music]
Tell me that.
- Why should I promise you?
♪ ♪
- Just tell me, are you gonna
make a big deal
of this tomorrow?
- Why should I promise you?
- Are you gonna make a big deal
of this tomorrow?
- Why should I promise you
anything, man?
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
You know what,
I sleep right here.
I'm trying to get some sleep.
Do me a favor
and excuse yourself.
♪ ♪
- Good night.
- And, hey, real quick.
Think about this one:
if you don't want me to worry
about what you and Hannah do,
don't talk about it.
♪ ♪
That's it.
The door is right there.
[dramatic music]
The door is right there!
- Sweet dreams, Luke.
[dramatic musical flourish]
[quiet music]
♪ ♪
- There's definitely nervous
excitement always going into,
you know, a Rose Ceremony,
and I'm always really curious
to see, like, how it, you know,
plays out in the end.
- I got a rose,
but still coming into tonight,
I would love to be able
to spend some time with her.
- I'm just excited to see her.
- Yeah.
[door clatters]
- [gasps]
- Oh!
- No way.
- Hey.
- What's up?
- I'm sorry to barge
in like this,
but, um...Luke,
can I talk to you for a second?
- Yes, would love to.
- She didn't look too happy.
- Has anything come up this
week that she might
have concerns about with Luke?
- I feel that Hannah is putting
one and two and three together.
- She had that face again.
- She did.
- Obviously, I have very
strong feelings for Luke,
but during the group date,
Luke brought up my
one-on-one date with Garrett
and the naked
bungee-jumping and...
how he feels about it.
- So what's up?
- We'll talk here in a second.
Since then,
I have been processing
what that conversation was
and how it made me feel,
and some of the things
that were said
still need to be addressed
to make sure that we're both
on the same page of who I am.
It was just really important
for me to talk to you.
Um...I so appreciate you
coming to me
and, um, having
a real conversation
and actually sharing concerns,
because I respect that a lot.
But the conversation,
it didn't sit well with me.
The issues were, like,
the language that you used
to describe
why you were upset.
You felt like it was
a slap in the face
because you want to spend
the rest of your life with me.
And then you said,
"We all make
boneheaded mistakes."
Oh, there was
one other thing that, like,
really hurt me that you said.
You were talking about me
meeting your family
and you wanted to be able to
feel confident in doing that
and it was like referring to,
like, the bungee jumping thing,
and I was like,
"Well, what does that mean
about me meeting
your family?"
I guess, like...
I told you, like,
it--it wasn't,
like, a--a sexual thing,
like, at all.
And it wasn't.
But even if it was...
[sighs]
At this point,
it doesn't matter
because you're not my husband.
You don't own my body.
You don't own me.
It's my body.
- I'm just--can
I start getting into...
- Yeah.
- Like, I'll be
completely honest.
I didn't--I didn't start--
I started the conversation
the worst way possible.
I started speaking on my mind
things I already assumed,
and I didn't give you a chance
to speak on it first.
And I definitely
have full trust in you
and that you will make
the right decisions because,
you know, right now, I am
laying my heart on the table.
And if you are the woman that
I will end up marrying one day,
then I have to have
that trust in you.
Let me just tell you this:
I don't really want to see
or know anything that you do
with the other guys 'cause I
don't even--like, even if I do,
I like--I--I'm, like--
like, stay in your own lane.
It's like I'm in a hallway.
I don't want to be able
to see through that wall,
you know what I mean?
I'm trying to focus on you
and what we have,
and I don't want any of that
to even cross my mind,
because then things
like this will happen.
And, like, this is--
this is good that we're having
this conversation because
I really appreciate the way
you're going about this 'cause
let me just tell you this:
I...am never gonna control you.
I will never tell you
what you can and can't do
with your body.
But let me get into things
I had brought up about,
you know, if I'm with you
and, I guess,
the verbiage I used was,
"If you ever made
a mistake or a boneheaded play
or something,"
I was not referring to that
whatsoever.
I was referring to,
in the future--
- But you did say, like, "It
felt like a slap in the face."
- I don't want to say
you're twisting my words but--
- That you want to be confident
about letting me meet
your family.
- Yeah, let me touch on that
too 'cause that's--that's--
I was totally
misunderstood there.
That thing,
I didn't--I didn't--
I wasn't even talking about
the bungee jumping thing
at all at that moment.
- Well, you were.
Yes, you were.
When we were
talking about that,
and it was, like,
in that same, like, breath.
- I'm--like,
I didn't mean that.
I was totally misunderstood
now that you're bringing it
to me that way
and I want you to know,
from day one,
I wanted you to meet my family,
but I just wanted--
- But, no, you literally said,
"I wanna be confident in that,"
and so--
- If I had said that,
I didn't...I didn't mean it.
I want you to be confident
and excited to meet my family.
I know that
I said some things
that could easily
have been misunderstood,
and I don't want you
to ever misunderstand me.
And I've been so excited
because our relationship
has finally been on track.
I feel like finally the train
is finally on the tracks now.
- I don't know
if it's on the tracks.
- Okay, even if it's not,
I feel like it's closer.
- It's not on the tracks.
No, I don't know!
I'm trying to figure out
my emotions
because it's, like--
it's like a flip-flop.
I'm like, "Yes, yeah, yeah,
I'm gonna keep trying."
Or, like, "Nope, don't wanna
do it anymore."
And so, like, I'm trying
to figure out how I feel.
- If you feel that way, look,
I'm sorry I was misunderstood,
but I--I didn't question
your character,
and I don't know
if you totally remember
everything I said
in that same breath--
- No, I do.
- But, Hannah, look,
I'm being completely real here.
I did not question
your character for one second.
- You said I was disrespectful.
You said I was disrespectful.
- Which was totally--I didn't--
I had no business saying that
because I hadn't even given you
the chance to touch on why.
And forgive me.
You know what, from now on,
I'm gonna speak clear
and I'm gonna be more careful
about the words I use,
'cause I don't ever want you
to misunderstand another thing
I say through this process
because it's tough.
- It's just getting,
like, so hard
because this is
every single time.
And, like...
- You know what? I'm--I'm
doing--I'm doing my best,
and if you feel like
you can't handle it,
I'm gonna continue
to try and fight harder
to do better,
but you know what?
Right now, I'm--
I'm giving you myself
and I'm giving you
the best I have,
and I'm gonna continue
to do better.
I mean, I don't know
what else to say
at this point
about this situation.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- It can't take this
every single time
for you to get to this point.
[voice shuddering]
I want a man that doesn't
take me screaming
and in your face
for you to finally,
like, be like this.
This process doesn't work
if you're not
yourself 100,000%,
and I need to know it's real
and it's all the time.
[tense music]
Like, why is it
so hard with us?
- I don't know, and it's been
completely my fault
that we have gotten here,
and I'm sorry.
And I'm telling you
this right now
and I mean it
with every part of me:
it will be worth it if you
just please keep fighting.
♪ ♪
- I don't know.
[dramatic musical flourish]
[church bell tolling]
- I mean, I talked
to Luke last night,
and I said, "You're
not staying in your own lane."
And he said, "Yes, I am.
"I'm driving my truck
in my own lane.
"I just looked out
the window to the left
"and I see you
and Hannah there
and I want to know
what's happening."
- My gosh.
- "It's my girlfriend,
just like
it's your girlfriend."
- That's not the same.
- "And I have a right
to know everything."
- He's saying he's
staying in his own lane
but looking out the window,
but I don't know if you guys
have ever driven a car...
- You swerve.
- But you can't stay
in your own lane
when you're looking out
the damn window at other cars.
[door clatters]
[lightly tense music]
- What's happening, fellas?
♪ ♪
Well, I know you guys
are gonna ask me,
so I'm just gonna get to it.
Um...
Well, one, for starters, what
Hannah and I just talked about
is something that's completely
between me and Hannah,
and I'm not gonna talk about it
with you guys.
And I'll also say this:
if there were details that
weren't spoken of,
like you from your date,
this wouldn't have even come up
to be a conversation
in the first place.
But I will say this too--
- So, hold on,
are you blaming him
for talking about his date?
- No, I'm saying thank you to
him for talking about his date.
- Oh.
- That's not what you told me
last night.
- Can you let me finish
real quick?
You know what she needs
right now from all of us?
And I'm not blaming anyone
for doing anything.
She needs us to stay
in our lanes completely.
And--
- But you weren't.
- I'm--I'm going to do that.
- No, you won't.
- Okay, regardless,
if we don't see eye to eye,
that's great.
I'm gonna continue
to stay in my lane.
- But you weren't--
you weren't in any lane.
- Hey, that's your opinion too.
If we don't see eye to eye,
great, okay?
I don't want to talk about
what we just talked about.
- No one's asking you to talk
about what you talked about.
- All right, great.
- We're just saying you're not
staying in your lane.
- Stay in your lane, you, you,
you, you, keep doing you.
- Keep puffing
your chest up, bro.
- Puffing my chest?
- Yeah.
- "You, stay in your lane,
stay in your lane,
stay in your lane."
You're trying to be
a big dog again and it's just--
- I'm not trying
to be a big dog.
- Listen to you.
- You weren't there when
he and I talked last night.
And guess who's trying
to be a big dog? That guy.
- How's he trying
to be a big dog?
Explain it.
- Again, you weren't
there last night.
- So explain it!
- He thinks I'm getting
in his lane--I'm not.
- You are!
You worried about his date.
- No, he's not, Tyler.
What he was doing
was looking out the window.
- Yeah.
- Oh, so you heard my analogy.
- That's how you crash, man.
That's how you crash.
- Yeah, don't text and drive.
- Here's what it is:
I told you how felt.
- I'm not puffing my chest,
though.
- You are, the way you,
"You, you, you"...
- Yeah, I don't know
why'd you point at me
because, like,
I've stayed in my lane.
I don't have [bleep]
to say to you.
- I don't have--listen.
I don't even want to talk
to you guys right now.
I have a lot to think about
between me and Hannah.
- Do you not think
it's a double standard
the fact that you're able
to parade around
in a Speedo
in front of everybody
and show your
big, bravado self,
but she can't go
jump off this--
you know, off a--
do bungee jumping?
- All right,
now you're getting into details
of something
between me and Hannah.
- I'm just asking you.
- Actually, details
between me and Hannah,
not between you and Hannah.
Let's get--let's
get that straight here.
That was
my one-on-one date, man,
and you're trying to tell her
what she can and can't do
on my one-on-one date.
- You're in his lane worrying
about what he's doing.
- First of all,
I never told Hannah
what she can and can't do.
When he came in here--
You guys can feel
the way you want to feel,
but when she came in here--
- You told her you were pissed
off at the way she acted.
- You gonna let me finish?
- No, because it's stupid.
- I'm trying to talk to my man
TC over here.
- No, because--
- Would you do me a favor
and keep your mouth shut
and let me get my point across?
- No, I'm not gonna keep my
mouth shut on this one, dude.
- Listen, I don't know how
you guys feel...
- There's no way.
- But when he's
standing right there
and he's explaining to us
what happened on his date,
yeah, I felt uncomfortable,
and I instantly--
regardless, you guys feel
the way you want to--
I wanted to get more details
'cause I felt like I needed
to know what happened.
- Why?
- Listen, that's
just how I felt, all right?
- Hey, Luke,
let's just keep it down here.
Last time when we got
started yelling, Hannah heard.
You don't know
if she's through that door.
and you [bleep] up
another cocktail thing,
you're gonna have me
really [bleep] pissed,
so let's keep it down.
We're all men.
I can hear you
just fine right here.
- Okay.
- Let's talk.
- I respect that.
Did you hear what Jed said?
'Cause I did, loud and clear,
and I'm not gonna
screw up tonight.
[door clatters]
- Fellas, what's going on?
- Chris, how's it going?
- How you doing?
- Hey, Chris.
- Is this everybody?
- Uh, yeah.
- Just saw Hannah,
and she was a little emotional.
- [sighs]
[tense music]
- There's not gonna be
a cocktail party tonight.
[dramatic music]
Going straight
to Rose Ceremony.
She knows exactly
what she wants to do.
So if you guys
would get dressed,
we'll see you at Rose Ceremony.
♪ ♪
- That's your [bleep] fault,
homie.
- Three in a row, Luke.
- [sighs]
[bleep].
- I just want you to know,
this isn't--
- It's your fault, bro.
Shut the [bleep] up.
- This isn't me.
This is totally
because this is
how Hannah feels.
- Three in a row.
- You take it how you want.
- Three in a row, Luke.
Keep it up.
- Not taking the blame
for this one, guys.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- Going into
this Rose Ceremony,
there's nine people
left here,
so Hannah does have
some tough decisions to make.
If Luke doesn't
go home tonight,
I think a lot of people will be
pretty upset about it.
♪ ♪
- Luke P. has successfully
taken away
Hannah's opportunities
to fully to get to know
everyone here.
I haven't talked to Hannah
for three cocktail parties
because of him.
I think if I were to go home
and Luke were to stay,
that's extremely frustrating.
- Wow.
- This is incredible.
- It's almost like
I have to keep looking down
and remember
that I have a rose
just because of all this drama
getting stirred up by Luke P.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I've been questioning it
for weeks now
why Luke P. is still around.
♪ ♪
Guy needs to go.
- [exhales]
I...really didn't know
what to expect
here in Latvia.
And although we did
have some struggles,
this week was great.
It really was.
And Riga did bring the romance
and the feeling of love
that I wanted it to,
and now I'm so excited
to say that
I really do think my husband
is in this room.
Y'all are all here
for a reason:
because I wanted to continue
to explore our relationships,
so I'm so glad that I have
each and every one of you
standing up here.
But I want to be in love
with one person
so completely and whole,
and to do that,
I have to start making
really hard choices,
but thank you all
for an incredible week
and an amazing journey to love.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Jed.
Jed, will you accept this rose?
- I will.
- [whispers indistinctly]
Mike.
Mike, will you
accept this rose?
- For my whiskey Southern
queen, absolutely.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Connor.
Connor, will you
accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
- Hannah, gentlemen, this
is the final rose tonight.
When you're ready.
- I know that Hannah's
been upset with me
and disappointed with me,
but I still believe
that I am her Mr. Right,
and there's no woman
in the whole entire world
I would rather
be fighting for.
Getting this rose would mean
she still has faith.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Luke.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [whispers]
Okay.
- Luke, will you
accept this rose?
- With all my heart.
[clears throat]
- Dylan, Dustin,
I'm sorry.
Take a moment,
say your good-byes.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- How's it going?
You okay?
- Sorry.
- No, don't apologize.
Good luck.
You're gonna do great, okay?
- Thank you for everything
that you shared with me.
- Uh-huh.
[clicks tongue]
It sucks.
Know what I mean?
And I may have not been
the right guy for her,
but it's pretty obvious
the type of person Luke is,
and I'm just hoping that
Hannah can realize it.
I just don't think her
and Luke are as compatible
as maybe some other
relationships in the house,
and I think 99% of the people
in there would agree with that.
- You're a beautiful girl,
and you're strong.
You're gonna find
your man out there.
These are great guys.
- Thank you, Dustin.
- I'm proud of you.
- Thank you.
- Rejection's a bitch.
You know,
it doesn't feel good.
I just didn't get the time
to show her who I was.
I really needed
that one-on-one
to show if it could
truly be a connection.
I would say for Luke
to get a rose,
the only thing
that I can come up with
is that she's
already in love with him.
I think if she wasn't,
he would have left
a long time ago.
- Here's to matching
Hannah's level of strength
that she's shown all of us
since the very beginning
and using every day
to be her rock.
- Cheers.
[glasses clink]
- I don't understand how Luke
can continue to stick around.
- I'll see you later, okay?
Yeah. Bye.
- There was a lot more heart in
the two guys that left tonight
than Luke will ever have.
- He's just not real.
I just never feel like
it's ever been real.
Quite frankly, I'm pretty
pissed with the whole thing.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- What?
- Let's keep each other
level-headed.
Let's get each other's back.
If we let him get to us,
it's all wasted, right?
- What do you like about Luke?
- I'm either falling
in love with Luke
or Luke is making me go crazy.
I'm not sure which one.
- Next week on
"The Bachelorette"...
- Whoo!
[bicycle bell ringing]
- We are in the Netherlands,
and I'm falling
for multiple guys
in totally different ways.
- I'm crazy about you.
both: Whoo!
- I have
no doubt in my mind
that we can take the world
on together and make it ours.
- I love you.
I'm buzzing off of nothing
but that moment.
- How could I not
be more confident?
She's falling in love
with me for sure.
[laughs]
It's like I know.
- You gave me your word.
Your "stay in your lane."
Like, it just,
like, doesn't end.
- I hope you're happy, man.
- He's gone, so guess what.
One less of us.
It's simple math.
- You're right, now there's
five guys who can't stand you.
We have a 5'8" villain.
- When he's faced with
something
that's confronting him,
the guy explodes.
- I don't care
what you said to her.
I've been nothing
but truthful with Hannah,
and you are not
gonna mess it up!
- [crying]
I don't know what to do.
I've never been surrounded
by, like, so much fighting,
and I'm scared.
[dramatic musical sting]
[gentle piano music]
- Let's make a Riga song.
- ♪ Oh, Riga ♪
♪ You've been so good to me ♪
- Oh.
- ♪ You're making me
fierce like a man ♪
♪ And I can't-- ♪
♪ And I can't help myself ♪
♪ Oh, Riga ♪
- ♪ Riga ♪
- There we go.
Bring me to church, boy.
[all cheer]
- ♪ I said, we gotta Riga! ♪
♪ I said, we gotta Riga! ♪
- We need a Riga!
- Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh,
ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
- Give it to me.
- You catching on, bro.
You catching on, [indistinct]?
You catching on,
[indistinct]?
You catching on!
- Whoo!
- Gimme a Riga!
all: Riga!
- Can I get a Riga?
- A Riga.
all: Riga!
- Let's slow it down
a little bit for the...
[plays soft piano chord]
♪ Oh, Riga ♪